Contact

glensgirl@sbcglobal.net

www.linkedin.com/in/ charlottefeatherston-msn-rncmsrn-16298978 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing BLS Hospitals

CharlotteFeatherston ,MSN, RN, CMSRN

University of Texas Medical Branch Friendswood. Texas

Summary

Experienced Administrator with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Budgeting, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Team Building, U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), and Healthcare Information Technology (HIT). Strong information technology professional with a Master of Science (MS) focused in Nursing Education from Grand Canyon University.

Experience

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Clear Lake Clinical Operations Administrator March 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months) Galveston, Texas

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston Emergency Room RN November 2016 - March 2019 (2 years 5 months) Galveston, Texas

Mainland Medical Ctr Nurse Manager and Administrator on Site September 2014 - June 2018 (3 years 10 months) Mainland Medical Center

Clear Lake Regional Medical Center Assistant Nurse Manager January 2010 - September 2014 (4 years 9 months)

San Jacinto Methodist Hospital Medical Technologist December 1990 - January 2010 (19 years 2 months) Bayside Community Hospital Laboratory Director May 1996 - June 2006 (10 years 2 months) Anahuac, Texas

Education

Grand Canyon University

Master of Science (MS), Nursing Education · (2015 - 2016)

The University of Texas Medical Branch at Galveston Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2011)

Alvin Community College

Associate of Science (AS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2007 - 2009)

San Jacinto College

Associate of Science (A.S.), Clinical Laboratory Science/Medical Technology/ Technologist · (1992 - 1994)

University of Mount Olive

Associate of Science (AS), Education · (1988 - 1990)